♪♪
Community of Southgate
was awakened just after midnight
once again by the sounds of sirens,
as firetrucks and ambulances rushed into
the area responding to a three-alarm fire.
This latest fire involved
two single-family homes
and the landmark Jones'
Tune and Fill service station
at the corner of Main
and Green Streets.
Two single-family homes
were destroyed quickly
as the fire spread from one
frame-and-shingle home to its neighbor.
Both homes are considered
destroyed beyond repair.
Sam and Lavinia Dumont, residents
of one of the destroyed homes,
said they woke to choking
smoke and crackling sounds of fire.
Officials were relieved
to hear from the Dumonts,
but their neighbors, John and Pat
McQueen and their three young children,
were away visiting
relatives in Florida
and therefore were not at risk in
the fire that destroyed their home.
Police and fire officials are once
again investigating for evidence of arson.
The mayor's office has set
up a special number to call
if you have any information about
this or the other Southgate fires.
Your call will be
kept confidential,
and there is a $10,000
reward for information
leading to the arrest and
conviction of anyone involved.
That number to call is 555-FIRE.
Jones' Tune and Fill,
once considered for preservation
by the city's historical society,
is now nothing more than a
pile of rubble and twisted steel.
Its loss is considered a blow
to the architectural, cultural,
and historical diversity of this city.
While there were no
injuries in last night's fire,
the anger and frayed nerves of the
remaining members of this community
were plain to see.
Oh, no.
Good morning, Ben, Conrad.
I thought you'd like to know.
What happened?
Sleeping pills.
Coroner's guessing she
took them about 8 last night.
He'll know more
after the autopsy.
Did she leave a note?
No. Looks like she just walked
in the door, poured herself a drink,
downed some pills,
and passed out and died.
It's my fault.
What?
If I had just gone
after her a little harder
on the stand, this
wouldn't have happened.
You can't know that, Ben.
What's Harvey
Kordell doing here?
He's her lawyer...
was her lawyer.
He's the one who found her.
Yesterday, when she left the
stand, she went straight to him
and explained her situation to
him and asked for his assessment.
He said that he told her
she was in serious trouble.
He was going to go
to court with her today.
Did she confess to
killing Doug Levitt?
Now, come on, Ben, even if she
had, you know you can't use it in court.
Lieutenant Brooks?
- I'll catch up with you all later.
- Yeah.
We've still got the guy
who sold her the detonator.
We don't know why
Diane killed Doug Levitt.
How can I plant
the seed of doubt
if we don't know that her motive
was at least as strong as our client's?
I'll be dag-goned... Flintrock.
Never heard of it.
Over 40 years old...
a very rare scotch.
Since when did you
become an expert on scotch?
Nelson Addleson told me.
He drinks it.
Your Honor, I move that all charges
against my client be dismissed.
We have the sworn statement of the
man who sold the detonator to Diane Becker.
We know who made the bomb.
We have the fact that, knowing that she
was about to be exposed as a murderer,
she went home and
committed suicide.
Clearly, my client is
innocent and she is guilty.
Diane Becker might as well
have signed a confession.
Your Honor, to say that
Mr. Matlock is overstating his case
would be a gross understatement.
Despite all the cartwheels
he's been turning,
my case against
Mr. Finley remains intact.
We have the tire tracks
from Mr. Finley's car,
which were found at
the scene of the murder.
I'm not turning cartwheels.
I've been working on this thing.
Did you know that
Diane Becker went out
and rented a car exactly like
my client's that very afternoon?
Did you know that?
We have the detonator
found in his garage.
She could have
dumped it there any time.
And we have the
testimony of five people
who all said that Bill Finley was mad as
hell at Doug Levitt for getting him fired.
And we have... Motion denied.
But, Your Honor...
But I will grant you a
one-day recess, Mr. Matlock,
inasmuch as your key
witness is no longer available.
I'll need five days,
Your Honor, at least.
Three days.
This court will be in recess
until 9 a.m. on Friday morning.
Nice try.
Ben, can we stop now?
It's after 2. I'm starving.
I can't stop. I've
got to get this done.
I've only got three days to
work on Bill Finley's case.
I'm still working on the case.
I'm making progress.
I'm getting in tight
with the gang, all right?
Dag-gone. There's
another car stopped.
How did he see that stop
sign with that bush in front of it?
Maybe he saw a little red,
and he knew it was a stop sign.
I'm not paying that ticket.
How much did that camera cost?
It's a rental.
Expensive, huh?
Some.
So you're into this
for a lot of cash now.
You've got two cameras,
you've got a tripod
and those boots you're
wrecking in the mud now.
Oh, no!
And now you wrecked your jacket.
Argh!
Ben, you've lost
perspective. Stop.
I'm not paying that ticket.
Forget it.
Hey, what are you doing, man?
You weren't in jail.
You killed my brother.
Yaah!
Come back here again,
boy, and you'll be dead.
You got that?
Who the hell are you?
I'm not sure, man.
- What are you doing?
- Research.
On what?
Addleson Enterprises. I
thought I told you to stay at home.
I'm going nuts there, Ben.
Well, work on your book.
I can't concentrate.
Well, meditate or something.
Oh, that stuff's a crock.
I mean, it's fine when
your biggest problem
is worrying about going on
camera with food stuck in your teeth,
but when you're facing the
prospect of going to prison for life,
somehow sitting around with your
fingers in circles just doesn't cut it.
Ben Matlock.
You are? How come?
No, it doesn't.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, thanks.
Thanks. Yeah. Keep in touch.
Yeah.
What?
Bob Brooks, Homicide.
He said the police are stepping up their
investigation into Diane Becker's death.
They're no longer
certain it was a suicide.
Why not?
They just found out that on her way
home from talking with her lawyer,
she stopped by a travel agent and
bought a one-way ticket to Brazil.
Why would she do that if she was
just going to go home and kill herself?
It doesn't make sense, does it?
And then the guy that Nelson
Addleson gave the money to
is known on the
streets as Reggie.
Apparently, he's some
kind of social worker...
Does a lot of work with gangs.
And this Reggie gives the
money to the gang members?
Right.
And they immediately went out,
and they fire bombed
this house in Southgate.
Anybody hurt?
No. Luckily, nobody was home.
Now there's another car stopped.
How can he see that sign
with that bush in front of it?
Because I told you, they see a little
red, and they figure it's a stop sign.
Maybe the wind blew that bush
away from that sign a little bit
from where it was
when I got stopped.
I'll fix it.
Yeah.
You're tampering with evidence.
I'm not tampering
with the evidence.
I'm just putting it
back the way it was.
If you move the bush...
I'm not tampering
with the evidence.
My friend Hattie
down at City Hall said
that Nelson Addleson's been buying
a lot of land down at Southgate lately.
He gets it real cheap because
everybody's so anxious to sell.
A lot of gang-related
violence down there lately.
There, that's better.
What I saw last night was
part of real estate scam?
Yeah. I'll just get some of
this lower stuff in a little closer.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Oh, Ben, I hate to be the one to tell you,
but you're working in poison ivy there.
There's no justice.
Come on. Let me get
something put on it.
Okay, get in the car.
We forgot the camera.
Oh.
That's all.
He didn't see the sign.
Ahem.
Mr. Matlock, good
to see you again.
- What's wrong with your hand?
- Oh, a little poison ivy.
It's nice of you to have lunch
with me on such short notice.
Well, it's a slow day again.
This recession's a killer.
- Itching?
- No.
Yes, gentlemen?
- Join me?
- No thanks.
- Glass of iced tea.
- All right.
Is that Flintrock?
This? Oh, no.
They don't stock that
here. It's hard to get.
That's why I was kind of surprised to
see a bottle of it at Diane Becker's house.
Did you give it to her?
Who?
Diane Becker, the news
anchor over at WDRN.
That woman that committed
suicide? No, I never met her.
Oh, I thought since Doug Levitt
used to produce her news program
that maybe he
introduced you to her.
No, he never did.
How about Reggie?
Where did you meet him?
Reggie?
That enterprising young man you gave
all that money to on the street yesterday.
You've been spying on me.
Yeah. Uh, sure.
You've been conspiring with
Reggie and his gang member friends
to force people to sell their
property in Southgate, haven't you?
Mr. Matlock, that's
one hell of a story.
But the truth is I met
Reggie at a charity banquet.
I liked what he had to say about his
work with the inner-city gang members,
and I made him a donation.
And you have a
problem with that?
Mr. Matlock?
Oh, well, I thought Reggie was
helping you purchase land cheap
so that when the city got ready for
their big renovation program downtown,
why, you'd have the
land that they needed.
You'd make a
fortune, Mr. Addleson.
What an imagination.
That's what Diane was drinking when she
took all those sleeping pills... Flintrock.
Well, if you're going to commit
suicide, you may as well go in style.
Yeah.
The police are no
longer sure it was suicide.
They think it may
have been murder.
An irate boyfriend?
They're not sure.
Me, I think it had something
to do with that false information
that she accidentally gave out
over the air about a month ago.
You made a fortune selling land
that was next to worthless, remember?
We've been through
this before, Mr. Matlock.
But only Doug Levitt was dead
then. Now Diane's dead, too.
And you think I'm a suspect?
Well, maybe the three
of you were in cahoots.
Maybe Doug Levitt got out of
line and you and Diane killed him.
And then maybe you killed Diane
because you realized how close I
was coming to breaking her down.
The night Diane died, I was at the
charity banquet that I told you about,
sponsored by the Policemen's
Association, from 7:30 to 10:00.
I was sitting at a table
surrounded by policemen.
How's that for an alibi?
Very good.
Thanks for the drink.
We're alone.
What the hell's going on?
Bill Finley's lawyer,
Ben Matlock.
I just found out he's
been having me tailed.
Why would he want to do that?
Because he thinks that I'm involved
with your murder... and Diane's, too.
Diane committed suicide.
Well, apparently, the
police don't think so.
- I think I'll leave town for a while.
- Oh, no.
No, you won't.
You want your share of the
20 million, you stay in town.
Why?
Because I need you.
- For what?
- To deliver some money.
Reggie's buddies want a raise.
The hell with them.
Hey, listen to me, Doug.
Four more cashouts and we've
got two square blocks in our pocket.
Now, I can't deliver the money, not
with Matlock breathing down my neck.
It will take you
all of 20 seconds.
What are you worried
about? You're already dead.
Remember?
- Yo, man, what you going to do?
- School is in session.
- Then do it, man.
- Bye-bye, yellow ball.
Yeah! Whoo!
- Yes.
- That's what I'm talking about.
Tuck-type magic.
Hey, Tuck, who's that dude
over there with Reggie, man?
- You ever seen him before?
- Catch you.
Yo, man, don't sweat that.
So what's going on, Tucker?
Business, homes. That's all.
You ain't got nothing against
making a little money, do you?
Course not.
How about raising a little hell?
I like that too.
You ever do them
both at the same time?
No.
You will tonight, my man.
Ha ha. Yeah.
Yeah, you will tonight.
- Now shoot.
- I am going to shoot.
Get it on, man. Let's go.
- Let's do it, man.
- Have a little tight match going, man.
- Hi, how are you doing?
- Fine.
Lovely dog.
Police!
He's not here.
Come on out of
there! Very slowly.
Blow this joint up, G.
Yeah, yeah, let's go!
You get paid for this?
Yeah. Sweet deal, ain't it?
Ha ha ha.
Yeah, G.
Yo, let's bust up.
Hey! Hey!
Get up out of there.
Get out of the car!
How did they get
here so fast, man?
- Let's go.
- We didn't do nothing.
Move over there.
Hey, what's up, man?
Get over there. Get over there
and put your hands on the car.
Stand very steady, gentlemen.
Don't make this your last day on earth.
You were lucky they let you go.
If I were the D.A., I'd have
thrown the book at you.
Come on, Ben, I was
just looking around.
You were trespassing
and in the house of the very
man you're accused of murdering.
That's not smart,
Bill. That's not smart.
But I found a clue.
When are you going to get it through
your thick skull that you're not a cop?
You're not an investigator.
You're not even a good reporter.
Is that what you think?
Hey. Isn't that...
So you found a clue? Good.
Let's go to the pancake house,
and you can tell me all about it.
Hey, Ben.
In here.
You're just in time.
Nothing like a little eggs and
potatoes and bacon and toast
after a hard night
in the slammer.
You look awful.
I have a headache,
and I can't imagine why.
After a night in the tank with
37 criminals, I should feel great.
Yeah, well, sit
down there and eat.
Who paid your bail? Reggie?
Yeah. One phone call, and he
was right there, cash in hand.
You were right on the money
about those gang members
getting paid to terrorize Southgate.
By Nelson Addleson?
Yeah, but the only
thing they know
is that somebody pays
Reggie, and Reggie pays them.
Ben, do you have any aspirin?
Yeah. it's, uh...
There's no way any of those
guys are going to rat on Reggie,
so I don't know what our
next move is going to be.
Oh, Ben. I got to have some.
- What, it's empty?
- Yes.
- Hey, Ben!
- In here.
Oh, great.
Reporting to us live from
the ozone layer, it's Bill Finley.
Morning.
Hey, you're out of jail.
That's great.
Ben told me how you
infiltrated that gang.
Scary stuff.
I went undercover once.
What did you pretend
to be? A reporter?
Ben, did you check
out that dentist?
Bill, it's not even
8:30 in the morning.
You haven't checked it out yet?
Checked out what?
Two days before he died,
Doug made a dentist appointment
with somebody who
wasn't his dentist.
What is he talking about?
Doug used the same
dentist for years.
He swore by him.
In fact, one of the few decent things
he ever did was turn me on to the guy.
And just before he died, he made
an appointment with somebody else.
I mean, why would he do something
like that... suddenly switch dentists?
It doesn't make sense.
What's the name
of this new dentist?
I told you last night.
- No, you didn't.
- Are you sure?
Bill, what's the name
of the new dentist?
I don't remember.
We'll be just a minute.
It's on his desk calendar
over here on the table.
- Where are you going?
- To get some aspirin.
Thomberg... that's
the new dentist's name.
The name of the guy he
used to go to is McClure.
Or is it McCoy?
Thanks, Bob.
I appreciate it.
Dr. Thomberg supplied the dental records
the police used to identify Doug Levitt.
His new dentist.
He was the only dentist in his
Rolodex, so people do change dentists.
Ben, when we were here before,
this bottle of blood pressure
medicine was full, right?
Yeah.
It's empty.
Did you...
What would I want with
Doug's blood pressure pills?
You don't suppose...
I need to speak to
Dr. Thomberg. It's an emergency.
- What's going on?
- Shh!
Doctor?
My name is Ben
Matlock. I'm an attorney.
I represent the man who's
accused of killing Doug Levitt.
I understand you did some
work on him just before he died.
Really?
He looked like he hadn't
seen a dentist in five years?
Doug? Yes, he had.
Doug Levitt was what?
About 5'11", 170 pounds,
brown hair, mustache.
Does that sound
about right to you?
The man who was with
him looked like that?
Doctor, what kind of work
did you do for Mr. Levitt?
$1,200 in bridge work?
Oh. He paid cash.
We have dental insurance.
Bill. It wasn't Doug.
Nope. I ain't selling.
Mr. Foster, you're not
going to get a better offer.
I ain't interested.
Everybody in the
neighborhood is selling.
Well, I'm not. Look, how
many times do I got to tell you?
This is my home.
It's been my home for 11 years,
and it's going to stay that way.
Even after what
happened last night?
I've had to deal with garbage
everywhere I've ever lived.
You're wasting your time.
Well, if you change
your mind, give us a call.
Ben Matlock.
Mr. Matlock? He was here.
Ben Matlock?
Judge Katz.
I certainly didn't
expect to see you here.
Well, I didn't expect to see you
here in traffic court, Judge Katz.
Just filling in,
Mr. Matlock. Just filling in.
Where's your client?
I'd like to see who's paying
your price to defend a traffic ticket.
Ahem. I'm defending
myself, Your Honor.
I'm the one who got the ticket.
Well... And you're pleading?
Not guilty.
Okay.
Here we go.
An interesting start to my day.
Let's hear from the officer.
He told me he didn't see the
stop sign, so I wrote him a ticket.
Anything to add, Sergeant?
Yes, sir.
I could see that that stop sign was
partly obscured by that little bush,
but I could still tell
it was a stop sign.
Now, wait a minute, Your Honor.
I'm just driving along at 35.
I did not see the stop sign.
I saw the bush, but I
did not see the stop sign.
I see.
Anything further,
Sergeant Turner?
Yes, sir. There's a flashing
light before that stop sign
that reads "Caution:
Stop sign 100 yards."
This doesn't look
good, Mr. Matlock.
But, Your Honor, I have pictures
of cars going through that stop sign.
Some stopped, but
a lot of them didn't.
I guess some of
them just got lucky.
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to fine you on the infraction.
But damn it, Your Honor,
I went to a lot of trouble
to get pictures of those cars
going lickety-split
through that stop sign.
It doesn't matter.
There was a warning
sign before the stop sign.
But damn it all, Your
Honor, I ruined my camera,
I ruined my boots, I tore my
suit, I got poison ivy on my hands,
and somebody ripped
the door right off my car
trying to get those pictures.
That's $61 for
the code violation
and another $61 for the use
of profanity in my courtroom.
But dag-gone, Your Honor...
Too late. Case is closed.
Pay on your way out.
Congratulations.
Say one word to me, and I'll deck
you right in front of that damn judge.
Can I say it was the principle?
He won't sell.
Oh, he will.
All he needs is
another incident.
Reggie's guys
just got out of jail.
They're not going to risk it.
For 10 grand,
they'll risk anything.
- You're going to give them 10 grand?
- No.
You are.
What's up, man?
What you going to do?
Oh, yeah. Is that what
you're going to do?
You're losing it, Conrad.
You're losing it,
homes. What's up?
Solid.
Hey, Reg.
We cool?
You got the ball.
Nice shot.
You wasted your shot, man.
Just shoot the ball, man.
You ain't going to make
it. No way. Just shoot.
Whoo-hoo!
Well, as I live and
breathe... Doug Levitt.
Get the hell away from me.
Don't be that way. I want you
to meet some of my friends.
This is Lieutenant Bob Brooks.
I'm Ben Matlock.
I figured you'd be making another drop
when Mr. Foster wouldn't sell his house.
Welcome back to the
land of the living, Mr. Levitt.
My name is not Levitt.
It's Holdren... James Holdren. Just
like it says on my driver's license.
So what does a fake license and
birth certificate cost these days, Doug?
A couple of grand?
The name is Jim.
You take the same blood
pressure medication as Doug Levitt.
So do a lot of people.
It's a coincidence.
Who really died
in that explosion?
What explosion?
You knew Diane
was setting you up,
so you set up somebody
else and watched him die,
and then you went
after Diane, didn't you?
Diane who?
Yeah.
Okay, we just checked your
fingerprints against Doug Levitt's.
I want to talk to my lawyer.
Wait just a minute, Doug.
Your practical
jokes are one thing,
but standing by and
watching me go to prison
for a murder that you knew
never happened, that really sucks.
Get him!
Who is this guy?
Get him out of here.
This really hurts.
Do you have some aspirin?
No.
I didn't know you could break
your hand punching somebody.
That never happens
in the movies.
If I had had any idea you were
going to punch out Doug Levitt,
I would have told you
it was going to hurt.
I was just going
to tell him off,
and then all of a sudden
my fist just took off.
Do you think he's serious about
what he said about suing me?
Yeah.
I'll plead insanity.
I'll back you up.
He's not going to sue you. He's
got too many troubles already.
They're really going to
charge him with the murder?
Yeah.
But if they don't know
who died in the explosion,
how are they going to prove
Doug was the murderer?
They're not.
Ben, why are we here?
I told you, we might
find something.
But the case is over.
Bill Finley's going to walk out of
court a free man tomorrow, right?
Yeah, and Doug Levitt will get
away with murder... two murders.
Let's see.
They found her
on the floor here.
Let's move this sofa.
Why?
Let's move it. We
might find something.
All right. Get that end.
Ohh. Lumbago, boy.
Ooh. Ooh. Ahh.
Ohh.
- Don't touch it.
- Don't touch it?
No. Don't touch it.
Mr. Matlock, in view
of recent events,
I would imagine there's
something you'd like to say.
Uh... thank you, Your Honor.
The defense would like
to call its final witness.
Witness?
But, counselor, the man your client
was accused of murdering is alive.
Surely you want
to move to dismiss?
Oh, I do.
But believe it or not,
in the interests of justice, it is
my duty to call this last witness.
- Really?
- Yes, ma'am. And my right.
Mr. Matlock, there is
no precedent for this,
but I am not going to waste everybody's
time by arguing, so call your witness.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Defense calls Mr. Doug
Levitt to the stand.
Well...
you look good for a dead man.
I mean real good.
Mr. Matlock.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Would you please explain to
the court who Nelson Addleson is?
He's a local real
estate developer.
- Are you and he friends?
- No.
Business partners?
I hardly know the man.
Hmm. Would you explain
these phone records
that indicate that you called each other
more than a dozen times last month?
I'll be glad to.
In fact, I'd be glad to explain
everything, if you're interested.
Oh, we are.
Well, last month, when I was still
producing the news for WDRN-TV,
Nelson Addleson called
me because Diane Becker,
my anchorwoman at
the time, had called him.
Now, it seems that
Diane had heard
that the zoning commission was
going to rezone a parcel of land
adjacent to
Mr. Addleson's farmland.
Well, she told
Mr. Addleson that for a price
she would make a
little mistake on the air.
She would make it seem like it
was his land that was being rezoned,
and, of course, its value
would skyrocket overnight.
Mr. Addleson refused her
offer, but she kept on calling him,
so he called me to see
if I could get her to quit.
I couldn't.
When I approached Diane, she
denied any wrongdoing whatsoever.
Unfortunately, my
boss, Howard Price,
heard about the calls that I'd
been making to Mr. Addleson,
and he presumed that I was responsible
for Diane's little mistake on the air.
He fired me.
Oh.
So I went back to Diane,
and I told her that I had
to tell Howard the truth,
even if it jeopardized
her career.
Well, Diane denied
everything again,
and then she told me that if I
ruined her career, she'd kill me.
Oh.
Well, I was scared.
So I figured the best thing to
do was just stay out of her way,
so I went down to Macon.
The next thing I knew, my summer
house at Sidney Lake had been blown up,
and I was supposed to be dead.
- She actually had tried to kill me.
- Yeah.
Well, now I was
really terrified.
I mean, I figured if she's crazy
enough to do a thing like that once,
she wouldn't
hesitate to try it again.
So I decided to just let everybody think
that I was dead, and I started a new life.
Uh, how did you intend to
make a living in this new life?
I hadn't quite figured
that one out yet.
You didn't go into
business with Mr. Addleson?
No.
You didn't help him use gangs to
intimidate people in the inner city
into selling their homes
cheap to Mr. Addleson?
No. Of course not.
Okay.
Uh, anything else?
No.
Well, that's a good story.
I mean, that's a
real good story.
But I don't think Diane Becker
frightened you out of town.
In fact, I don't think
you left town at all.
I think you, Diane Becker,
and Nelson Addleson conspired
to air that false rezoning story
and then split the huge profit that
Nelson Addleson made as a result.
Now that's ridiculous.
Just speculating,
Mr. Levitt. Just speculating.
I think Diane got greedy,
and she played what looked like
a practical joke on Mr. Finley here,
knowing he'd be
fired and blame you.
Then she blew up your summer cottage
to kill you, and the police blamed him.
And then she went
to Mr. Addleson
and demanded your share of
the profits as well as her own.
What she didn't know
is that you had already
figured out what she was up to.
And I think that sometime
before the explosion,
you found somebody to take your
place, dressed him in your clothes,
put your watch on him, made sure he
was in that cabin when she blew it up.
No. No, I didn't. I was in...
Now this isn't
speculation, this is fact.
You took this unknown person
to a dentist... a Dr. Thomberg...
And he did extensive
dental work on him.
And you took him there as Doug
Levitt, introduced him as Doug Levitt.
There could only be one
reason for this strange action...
You knew that when the police went
looking for Doug Levitt's dental records,
this man's would be
the ones they would find.
No, I didn't.
Dr. Thomberg
identified you as the man
who brought this "Doug
Levitt" to his office.
Then Dr. Thomberg
made a mistake.
You set this poor man
up to die in your place.
Diane Becker pushed the button, but
as sure as you're alive, you killed him.
You can't prove that,
Mr. Matlock. I think you know that.
No.
No, I can't.
But the good news is I can
prove you killed Diane Becker.
I thought Diane Becker
committed suicide.
Everybody thinks she committed suicide
because you made it look like suicide.
No, I didn't.
You went over to
her house that night,
and you forced that bottle of
sleeping pills down her throat.
And then you wiped your
prints off of everything
and made sure that her prints were
on the glass and the empty bottle.
No. I didn't.
You recognize this?
No.
That's one of Diane
Becker's sleeping pills.
Mr. Conrad McMasters found it
on the floor of her condominium.
I guess you didn't
know you dropped it.
You know what the police
found when they examined it?
Two prints... a thumbprint
and an index finger print...
And they weren't Diane's
prints. They were yours.
No.
Mr. Levitt, it's over.
Hey, Bill, congratulations.
There he is!
- Hey!
- You look great.
Howard, what's going on?
A little celebration, Bill.
Not only is your trial over, but
you've got your old job back.
That is, if you want it.
You bet I do.
I don't blame you.
Thanks again, Ben.
You'll get my bill.
That's why I'm
shaking your hand now.
www.tvsubtitles.net